<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>FAQ on HedgeDoc - Collaborative markdown editor</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/faq/</link><description>Recent content in FAQ on HedgeDoc - Collaborative markdown editor</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>The HedgeDoc developers. Theme based on [vex-hugo](https://github.com/themefisher/vex-hugo).</copyright><atom:link href="https://hedgedoc.org/faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How stable is the demo instance?</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/faq/demo-instance-stability/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/faq/demo-instance-stability/</guid><description>In the past, the number of problems with our demo instance was very low, but we don’t guarantee that your notes won’t be lost because of hardware or software malfunctions.</description></item><item><title>Why does the demo instance use Cloudflare?</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/faq/cloudflare/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/faq/cloudflare/</guid><description>Some countries have a too high latency to the demo instance, which means HedgeDoc would be unusable. To make the demo available in as many countries as possible, we use Cloudflare.</description></item><item><title>Can I run multiple instances on the same database?</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/faq/multiple-instances/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/faq/multiple-instances/</guid><description>No. The HedgeDoc server process is not entirely stateless and therefore running more than one instance will result in missing/broken content for users.</description></item><item><title>Why is CodiMD now called HedgeDoc?</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/faq/rename-from-codimd-to-hedgedoc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/faq/rename-from-codimd-to-hedgedoc/</guid><description>The short version: There were two CodiMD-projects on GitHub, the community-driven fork and the original project maintained by the HackMD-team. To solve this naming conflict, our community-driven version was renamed to HedgeDoc.</description></item><item><title>Why was the PDF Export feature removed?</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/faq/pdf-export-removed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/faq/pdf-export-removed/</guid><description>We used a chrome-headless instance to generate the PDFs, but that led to some security vulnerabilities and was therefore deactivated. There are currently plans to re-add this feature in a safe way, but this will most likely take some time and can be expected at the earliest with 2.</description></item></channel></rss>