<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>HedgeDoc - The best platform to write and share markdown. on HedgeDoc - Collaborative markdown editor</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/</link><description>Recent content in HedgeDoc - The best platform to write and share markdown. on HedgeDoc - Collaborative markdown editor</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>By the HedgeDoc developers. Made with ![love](/images/heart.svg)️ and [Hugo](https://gohugo.io/).</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 19:35:20 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hedgedoc.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.9.8</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.8/</link><pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 19:35:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.8/</guid><description>Please note: This release dropped support for Node 14, which is end-of-life since May 2023. You now need at least Node 16 to run HedgeDoc.</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.9.7</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.7/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 21:36:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.7/</guid><description>Bugfixes Fix note titles with special characters producing invalid file names in user export zip file Fix night-mode toggle not working when page is loaded with night-mode enabled Contributors Francesco (translator) Gabriel Santiago Macedo (translator)</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.9.6</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.6/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 22:10:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.6/</guid><description>Bugfixes Fix migrations deleting all notes when SQLite is used</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.9.5</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.5/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2022 21:15:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.5/</guid><description>🚨 This release has a bug that leads to data-loss when using SQLite. We advise users of SQLite databases to skip this release and use 1.</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.9.4</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.4/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 20:06:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.4/</guid><description>Please note: This release dropped support for Node 12, which is end-of-life since April 2022. You now need at least Node 14.</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.9.3</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.3/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 20:19:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.3/</guid><description>This release fixes a security issue. We recommend upgrading as soon as possible.
⚠️ Warning: If you deploy HedgeDoc and MariaDB with docker-compose using a checkout of our container repo, you will need to manually convert the character set of the database to utf8mb4 when updating.</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.9.2</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 20:05:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.2/</guid><description>Bugfixes Fix error in the session handler when requesting /metrics or /status</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.9.1</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Dec 2021 21:18:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.1/</guid><description>This release increases the minimum required Node versions to 12.20.0, 14.13.1 and 16. In general, only the latest releases of Node 12, 14 and 16 are officially supported by us, older minor versions can be dropped at any time.</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.9.0</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 20:22:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.9.0/</guid><description>Security Fixes CVE-2021-39175: XSS vector in slide mode speaker-view This release removes Google Analytics and Disqus domains from our default Content Security Policy, because they were repeatedly used to exploit security vulnerabilities.</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.8.2</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.8.2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2021 19:41:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.8.2/</guid><description>This release fixes two security issues. We recommend upgrading as soon as possible.
Security Fixes CVE-2021-29503: Improper Neutralization of Script-Related HTML Tags in Notes Fix a potential XSS-vector in the handling of usernames and profile pictures</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.8.1</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.8.1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2021 20:37:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.8.1/</guid><description>Enhancements Speed up yarn install in production mode (as performed by bin/setup) by marking frontend-only dependencies as dev-dependencies. This also reduces the size of the docker container Speed up the frontend-build by using esbuild instead of terser to minify JavaScript Improve behavior of the &amp;lsquo;Quote&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;List&amp;rsquo;, &amp;lsquo;Unordered List&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Check List&amp;rsquo; buttons in the editor to automatically apply to the complete first and last line of the selection Bugfixes Correct the 1.</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.8.0</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.8.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2021 20:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.8.0/</guid><description>This release fixes multiple security issues. We recommend upgrading as soon as possible.
Please note: This release dropped support for Node 10, which is end-of-life since April 2021.</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.7.2</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.7.2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 15 Jan 2021 20:25:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.7.2/</guid><description>This release fixes a security issue. We recommend upgrading as soon as possible.
Security Fixes CVE-2021-21259: Stored XSS in slide mode</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.7.1</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.7.1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 20:21:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.7.1/</guid><description>This release fixes two security issues. We recommend upgrading as soon as possible.
Security Fixes CVE-2020-26286: Arbitrary file upload
An unauthenticated attacker can upload arbitrary files to the upload storage backend.</description></item><item><title>HedgeDoc 1.7.0</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.7.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Dec 2020 21:53:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.7.0/</guid><description>We have renamed to HedgeDoc! 🎉
Many thanks to Éric Gaspar who designed our new logo!
Have a look at our new website (which also explains the reasoning behind the renaming) at https://hedgedoc.</description></item><item><title>CodiMD 1.6.0</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.6.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 23:18:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.6.0/</guid><description>Announcements After the 1.6 release we will start to develop Version 2.0, which will introduce breaking changes. But we will take care of making your way to 2.</description></item><item><title>CodiMD 1.5.0</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.5.0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2019 21:30:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.5.0/</guid><description>Announcements There is a new docker image available by LinuxServer.io providing an ARM container Disabling PDF export due to security problems Enhancements Add migration guide for Node version 6 Add functionality to respect Do-Not-Track header Add Arabian translation Fixes Fix styling in slide preview Fix some lint warning Upgrade Sequelize to version 5 Add Linuxserver.</description></item><item><title>CodiMD 1.4.0</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.4.0/</link><pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2019 23:09:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.4.0/</guid><description>Announcements CodiMD now has a Mastodon account CodiMD now has a community forum With CodiMD 1.4.0 we&amp;rsquo;re dropping node 6 support.</description></item><item><title>CodiMD 1.3.2</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.3.2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2019 11:34:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.3.2/</guid><description>Announcement CodiMD is now running in an own organization. Check out our vision for the future Fixes Update various links to the new repositories Fix background color for mode switching button in night mode</description></item><item><title>CodiMD 1.3.1</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.3.1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 23 Mar 2019 12:28:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.3.1/</guid><description>Enhancements Add some missing translations Add Serbian language Fixes Fix broken redirect for empty serverURL Fix wrong variable type for HSTS maxAge Fix GitLab snippets showing up without being configured Fix Google&amp;rsquo;s API after disabling Google+ Fix broken PDF export Contributors atachibana (translator) Aurélien JANVIER (translator) Daan Sprenkels (translator) Farizrizaldy (translator) Luclu7 Sylke Vicious (translator) toshi0123 &amp;amp; okochi-toshiki Turakar Vladan (translator)</description></item><item><title>CodiMD 1.3.0</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.3.0/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2019 11:38:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.3.0/</guid><description>Enhancements Run db migrations on npm start Add documentation about integration with AD LDAP Add rel=&amp;quot;noopener&amp;quot; to all links Add documentation about integration with Nextcloud for authentication Update URL on frontpage to point to codimd.</description></item><item><title>CodiMD 1.2.1</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.2.1/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Oct 2018 14:25:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.2.1/</guid><description>Enhancements Update Italian translations Update Japanese translations Update markdown-pdf Add support for unix sockets Update &amp;ldquo;follow us&amp;rdquo; information to Community channel and translation Add Cloudron installation method Add guide for Mattermost authentication Update various packages Add Indonesian language as new translation Fixes Fix content types in status router Fix some modal colors in night mode Fix CSP to allow usage of speaker notes Fix some wrong title attributes in the editor toolbar Fix some confusion about the default location of images.</description></item><item><title>CodiMD 1.2.0</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.2.0/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jun 2018 17:39:59 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/releases/1.2.0/</guid><description>Announcement HackMD CE is renamed to CodiMD to prevent confusion. For details see here Enhancements Show full title by hovering over to table of contents entries Add generic OAUTH2 support for authentication Redirect unauthenticated user to login page on &amp;ldquo;forbidden&amp;rdquo; pages Add ability to add ToS and privacy documents without code changes Add account deletion as part of user self-management Add download of all own notes Add privacy policy example (no legal advice) Increase checkbox size on slides Add support for Azure blob storage for image uploads Add Korean translation Add note about official K8s chart for deployment Add toolbar for markdown shortcuts in editor Add ability to disable Gravatar integration Add print icon to slide menu which leads to the print view.</description></item><item><title>Demo instance</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/demo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/demo/</guid><description>The demo instance is a publicly available instance for trying out HedgeDoc and can be found at demo.hedgedoc.org.
While notes and accounts on the demo instance are not deleted periodically, you should not rely on the demo instance for production use.</description></item><item><title>History</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/history/details/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/history/details/</guid><description>If you don&amp;rsquo;t like text, there is also a visual explanation.
It started with HackMD HackMD is the origin of this project, which was mostly developed by Max Wu and Yukai Huang.</description></item><item><title>Privacy Policy</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/privacy-policy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/privacy-policy/</guid><description>Preamble: Hosting Details The HedgeDoc landing page is a static site that does not track, collect, store any information, or set any cookies.</description></item><item><title>Redirect to release page</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/latest-release/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/latest-release/</guid><description> If your browsers doesn't redirect you to the release page, then click here</description></item><item><title>Team</title><link>https://hedgedoc.org/team/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hedgedoc.org/team/</guid><description>Core Developers David Mehren davidmehren Maintainer, Backend Yannick Bungers InnayTool Backend Erik Michelson ErikMichelson Frontend Tilman Vatteroth mrdrogdrog Frontend Sheogorath SISheogorath Server, Backend Éric Gaspar ericgaspar Logo Design Claudius Coenen ccoenen Frontend Philip Molares DerMolly Frontend, Backend Nick Sweeting pirate CLI Hugo Peixoto hugopeixoto Container</description></item></channel></rss>